Finding aid for Thomas Yoder papers, 1967-1991
Bentley Historical Library
- Sound Recordings
  - Audiocassette Tapes
    - Recordings of conference talks and prayer meetings, 1969-1972
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 May 08; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-37-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] North Subcommunity - (Sunday), 1972 May 14; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-38-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 May 14; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-39-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Education] Dr. Henry Brandt, [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-40-1]; mp3 file; (Dr. Henry Brandt leads a prayer meeting and reads from scriptures and psalms.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-40-2]; mp3 file; (Dr. Henry Brandt leads a prayer meeting and reads from scriptures and psalms.)
      - [Education] Peter Collins at FC II on Bruderhof, [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-41-1]; mp3 file; (Peter Collins discussing the Bruderhof religious community.)
      - [Education] Michael Harper MSD discussion #2, [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-42-1]; mp3 file; (Michael Harper visiting the community discussing religious communities in Britain and other places. Also discusses the role of women in the Church.)
      - [Education] Loretta Martin "Serving the Lord", [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-43-1]; mp3 file; (Loretta Martin talk entitled "Serving the Lord.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-43-2]; mp3 file; (Loretta Martin talk entitled "Serving the Lord.")
      - [Education] Kathryn Kuhlman; Healing Service; Melodyland Charismatic Clinic, 1969 August; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-44-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Sermon and Healing service lead by Kathryn Kuhlman. Includes portions from what appear to be radio dramas and other Christian broadcast programs.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-44-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Sermon and Healing service lead by Kathryn Kuhlman. Includes portions from what appear to be radio dramas and other Christian broadcast programs.)
      - [Education] Kathryn Kuhlman; Healing Service; Melodyland Charismatic Clinic, 1969 August; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-45-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Sermon and Healing service lead by Kathryn Kuhlman. Includes portions from what appear to be radio dramas and other Christian broadcast programs.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-45-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Sermon and Healing service lead by Kathryn Kuhlman. Includes portions from what appear to be radio dramas and other Christian broadcast programs.)
      - [Education] Sunday; Monday, 1970 September 06-07; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-46-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-46-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Education] Covenant Ceremony, 1970 September 28, 1970 November 23; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-47-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-47-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Education] Ralph Martin "History of the Word of God"; Steve Clark "What It Means To Be A People, One Body", 1970 October 30, 31, November 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-48-1]; mp3 file; (1970 October 30, 31; Ralph Martin talk entitled "History of the Word of God.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-48-2]; mp3 file; (1970 October 31, November 01; Steve Clark talk entitled "What It Means to be A People, One Body.")
      - [Education] Steve Clark "Elements of the Covenant"; Ralph Martin "Finding Our Place In The Community", 1970 October 31, November 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-49-1]; mp3 file; (1970 October 31; Steve Clark talk entitled "Elements of the Covenant.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-49-2]; mp3 file; (1970 November 01; Ralph Martin talk entitled "Finding Our Place in the Community.")
      - [Education] Bishop McKinney: homily at Ann Arbor; Bishop Levin: homily at Ann Arbor, Bishop Schoener, 1971 January 01-03; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-50-1]; mp3 file; (Bishop McKinney giving a Homily in Ann Arbor.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-50-2]; mp3 file; (Bishop Levin giving a Homily in Ann Arbor; sermon by Bishop Schoener.)
      - [Education] Jim Cavnar "Better Prayer Meetings" Workshop at National Leaders Conference, 1971 January 03; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-51-1]; mp3 file; (Jim Cavnar workship enttiled "Better Prayer Meetings.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-51-2]; mp3 file; (Jim Cavnar workship enttiled "Better Prayer Meetings.")
      - [Education] Covenant Renewal IV, 1971 March 29; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-52-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-52-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Education] Covenant Renewal IV, 1971 March 29; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-53-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-53-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Education] Doug Gavriledes; "Service in the Body of Christ", Service Day, 1971 October 16; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-54-1]; mp3 file; (Doug Gavriledes talk entitled "Service in the Body of Christ.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-54-2]; mp3 file; (Doug Gavriledes talk entitled "Service in the Body of Christ.")
      - [Education] Bruce Yocum "Salvation"; Don Swager "Work of the Holy Spirit in our lives", 1971 November 20; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-55-1]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum talk entitled "Salvation.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-55-2]; mp3 file; (Don Swager talk entitled "Work of the Holy Spirit in Our Lives.")
      - [Education] Service Day, 1971 December 18; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-56-1]; mp3 file; (Lecture and sermon on the discussion of the Charismatic movement.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-56-2]; mp3 file; (Lecture and sermon on the discussion of the Charismatic movement.)
      - [Education] Father Francis McNutt, "Healing" - NSC; Bobby Cavnar "Deliverance" - NSC, 1971 December 31, 1972 January 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-57-1]; mp3 file; (Father Francis McNutt talk entitled "Healing.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-57-2]; mp3 file; (Bobby Cavnar talk entitled "Deliverance.")
      - [Education] Michael Harper; LSD Take #2, 1972 February 19; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-58-1]; mp3 file; (Michael Harper lecturing on the Catholic Pentacostal movement.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-58-2]; mp3 file; (Michael Harper lecturing on the Catholic Pentacostal movement.)
      - [Education] Michael Harper; LSD Take #1, 1972 February 19; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-59-1]; mp3 file; (Michael Harper lecturing on the Catholic Pentacostal movement.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-59-2]; mp3 file; (Michael Harper lecturing on the Catholic Pentacostal movement.)
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Ralph Martin "The Second Coming"; Peter Williamson "The Second Coming"; Ralph Martin "It just doesn't fit", 1970 November 19, 1970 December 10, 1971 January 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-60-1]; mp3 file; (Two talks R. Martin "2nd Coming" for the first forty minutes, and P. Williamson "2nd Coming" to the end of the tape.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-60-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin prayer meeting entitled "It Just Doesn't Fit.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Steve Clark "Humility"; Jim Cavnar "Guidance", 1971 March 11, 1971 March 15; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-61-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Humility.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-61-2]; mp3 file; (Jim Cavnar talk entitled "Guidance.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Randy Cirner on various hastles and how to deal with them; Ralph Martin on the Resurrection, 1971 March; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-62-1]; mp3 file; (Randy Cirner on various kinds of personal problems and how to deal with them and R. Martin on the subject of the Resurrection.)
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Steve Clark "Community Schedule", Steve Clark on the Sabbath and Supper Hour; Steve Clark "Households", 1971 May 05, 1971 May 19; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-63-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talking on "Community Schedule.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-63-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark on the Sabbath and Supper Hour; Steve Clark talking on "Households.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Ralph Martin "On what the Lord is doing among us: Making us into a body"; Ralph Martin "Hospitality", 1971 May 12, 1971 May 19, 1971 May 26; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-64-1]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin on "On What the Lord is doing among us: Making us into a body.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-64-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin giving a sermon on "Hospitality.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Steve Clark "Headship and Subordination"; Bruce Yocum "Hope", 1971 June 02, 1971 June 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-65-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark on "Headship and Subordination.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-65-2]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum sermon entitled "Hope.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Ralph Martin "Homecoming Weekend"; "Kingdom of God and the world", 1971 July 03, 1971 August 19; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-66-1]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin on "Homecoming Weekend.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-66-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin on "Kingdom of God and the World.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Steve Clark "Faith"; Chris Gramlich "Who is God?", 1971 September 16, 1971 September 23; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-67-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk from prayer meeting entitled "Faith.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-67-2]; mp3 file; (Chris Gramlich at a prayer meeting giving a talk entitled "Who is God?")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Chris Gramlich "Idolatry"; Bruce Yocum "The Word of the Lord", 1971 July 15, 1971 September 30; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-68-1]; mp3 file; (Chris Gramlich giving a talk entitled "Idolatry."; Bruce Yocum on "The Word of the Lord.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-68-2]; mp3 file; (Chris Gramlich giving a talk entitled "Idolatry."; Bruce Yocum on "The Word of the Lord.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Jim Cavnar "Prophecy"; Steve Clark "The promised the Lord has made to us", 1971 July 26, 1971 October 18; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-69-1]; mp3 file; (Jim Cavnar talk entitled "Prophecy.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-69-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "The promised the Lord has made to us.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Ralph Martin "The Cross of Jesus Christ"; "The word the Lord is speaking to us on freedom", 197 October 21, 1971 October 04; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-70-1]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin talk on "The Cross of Jesus Christ.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-70-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin talk entitled "The word the Lord is speaking to us on freedom.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Steve Clark "Faith"; Ralph Martin "Things the Lord is freeing us from", 1971 October 28, 1971 October 25; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-71-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Faith")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-71-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin talk entitled "Things the Lord is freeing us From.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Bob Bell "God's love for us"; Steve Clark, Randy Cirner on "Christmas", 1971 November 18, 1971 November 22, 1971 December 06; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-72-1]; mp3 file; (Bob Bell talk entitled "God's Love for us.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-72-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark and Randy Cirner talking on "Christmas.")
      - [Education, Talks from Prayer Meetings] Bruce Yocum "The Second Coming"; Peter Williamson "The Second Coming", 1971 December 02, 1971 December 09; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-73-1]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum talk entitled "The Second Coming.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-73-2]; mp3 file; (Peter Williamson talk entitled "The Second Coming.")
      - [Education, Talks from General Community Gathering], Ralph Martin "Life in the Spirit", [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-74-1]; mp3 file; (Part I; Ralph Martin on "Life in the Spirit.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-74-2]; mp3 file; (Part I; Ralph Martin on "Life in the Spirit.")
      - [Education] Prophecy Workshop, [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-75-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; A speaker discussing the use of prophecies in the Charismatic movement.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-75-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; A speaker discussing the use of prophecies in the Charismatic movement.)
      - [Education] Prophecy Workshop, [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-76-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; A speaker discussing the use of prophecies in the Charismatic movement.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-76-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; A speaker discussing the use of prophecies in the Charismatic movement.)
      - [Education] January Leaders weekend retreat, [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-77-1]; mp3 file; (Part 1; Steve Clark speaking on "Service (Christian manhood)")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-77-2]; mp3 file; (Part 2; Steve Clark lecturing on "Establishing Priorities.")
      - [Education talks from General Community Gathering] Jim Cavnar "Person and work of the Holy Spirit"; "Normal life in the Spirit", [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-78-1]; mp3 file; (Jim Cavnar talk entitled "Person and work of the Holy Spirit.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-78-2]; mp3 file; (Jim Cavnar talk entitled "Normal life in the Spirit.")
      - [Education talks from General Community Gathering] Bruce Yocum "Turn to the Lord!"; Tommy Tyson "Life in the Spirit", [Undated], 1969 January 03; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-79-1]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum talk entitled "Turn to the Lord!")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-79-2]; mp3 file; (Tommy Tyson talk entitled "Life in the Spirit.")
      - [Education] Steve Clark "Salvation" NSC; Ralph Martin "The World, Satan, and Christian Community" NSC, 1971 December 31; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-80-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Salvation")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-80-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin talk entitled "The World, Satan, and Christian Community.")
      - [Education] Steve Clark "The Word Gifts" NSC; Bruce Yocum "The Word Gifts", 1971 December 31; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-81-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "The Word Gifts.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-81-2]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum talk entitled "The Word Gifts")
      - [Education] Ralph Martin "Freedom From Sin, Satan, and Disease" NSC; Steve Clark "Becoming a Christian" NSC, 1972 January 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-82-1]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin talk entitled "Freedom from Sin, Satan, and Disease.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-82-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Becoming a Christian.")
      - Fall Conference, Steve Clark "Introduction"; Ralph Martin "State of Community", 1972 September 08; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-83-1]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin introducing the Fall Conference.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-83-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin at Fall Conference talking on the "State of the Community.")
      - Fall Conference, Steve Clark "Exclusion", 1972 September 09; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-84-1]; mp3 file; (Talk given by Steve Clark at Fall Conference on the topic of "Exclusion".)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-84-2]; mp3 file; (Talk given by Steve Martin at Fall Conference on the topic of "Exclusion".)
      - Fall Conference, Bruce Yocum "Exclusion", 1972 September 09; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-85-1]; mp3 file; (Talk given by Bruce Yocum at Fall Conference on the topic of "Exclusion".)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-85-2]; mp3 file; (Talk given by Bruce Yocum at Fall Conference on the topic of "Exclusion".)
      - Fall Conference, Exclusion General Discussion, 1972 September 09; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-86-1]; mp3 file; (Discussion of the structure and directions of the community.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-86-2]; mp3 file; (Discussion of the structure and directions of the community.)
      - Fall Conference, Finances, Steve Clark, 1972 September 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-87-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark discussing the spiritual and financial directions of the community.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-87-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark discussing the spiritual and financial directions of the community.)
      - Fall Conference, Finances, Discussion, 1972 September 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-88-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark discussing the spiritual and financial directions of the community. Community members are also discussing.)
      - [Talks from Conferences] Jim Byrne "Faith, Conversion, and the Church Today", [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-89-1]; mp3 file; (Jim Byrne talk entitled "Faith, Conversion, and the Church." Cassette box reads "Conversation", cassette itself reads "Conversion.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-89-2]; mp3 file; (Jim Byrne talk entitled "Faith, Conversion, and the Church." Cassette box reads "Conversation", cassette itself reads "Conversion.")
      - [Talks from Conferences] Bert Ghezzi "Learning to Love One Another", [Undated]; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-90-1]; mp3 file; (Bert Ghezzi talk entitled "Learning to Love One Another.")
      - [Talks from Conferences] Bruce Yocum "Prophecy", 1971; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-91-1]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum talk entitled "Prophecy" from 1971 National Conference.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-91-2]; mp3 file; (Bruce Yocum talk entitled "Prophecy" from 1971 National Conference.)
      - [Talks from Conferences] Steve Clark "Community Order"; "Spiritual leadership"; "Finding our place as leaders in the community", 1971 January 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-92-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Community Order," "Spiritual Leadership",)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-92-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Finding our place as leaders in the community.")
      - [Talks from Conferences] Gerry Rauch "Psychological problems", 1971 January 03; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-93-1]; mp3 file; (Jerry Rauch talk entitled "Psychological Problems.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-93-2]; mp3 file; (Jerry Rauch talk entitled "Psychological Problems.")
      - [Talks from Conferences] Steve Clark "Establishing priorities"; Ralph Martin more on "Godly Man", 1971 January 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-94-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk entitled "Establishing Priorities.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-94-2]; mp3 file; (Ralph Martin talk entitled "Godly Man.")
      - [Talks from Conferences] Steve Clark on "Godly Man II Time", 1971 January 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-95-1]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk enttiled "Godly Man", continued from previous tape.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-95-2]; mp3 file; (Steve Clark talk enttiled "Godly Man", continued from previous tape.)
      - Bert Ghezzi "Ongoing Conversion -- Surrendering to Christ" Community Formation Day Talk #1, 1971 April 18; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-96-1]; mp3 file; (Bert Ghezzi talk entitled "Ongoing Conversion: Surrendering to Christ.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-96-2]; mp3 file; (Bert Ghezzi talk entitled "Ongoing Conversion: Surrendering to Christ.")
      - [Talks from Conferences] Ralph Martin "Mystery of the Resurrection and the Last Day"; David DuPlessie testimony, 1971 April 18, 1971 April 22; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-97-1]; mp3 file; (Providence, R.I., Day of Renewal. Ralph Martin talk entitled "Mystery of the Resurrection and the Last Day." Also includes David DuPlessie testimony.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-97-2]; mp3 file; (Providence, R.I., Day of Renewal. Ralph Martin talk entitled "Mystery of the Resurrection and the Last Day." Also includes David DuPlessie testimony.)
      - Jim Cavnar "Faith"; Communty Day, 1st Talk, 1971 May; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-98-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of Jim Cavnar talk entitled "Faith.")
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-98-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of Jim Cavnar talk entitled "Faith.")
      - Jim Cavnar, "Spiritual Power In the Body of Christ"; Community Day, 2nd Talk, 1971 May 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)